[English subtitles are available]
I have already told you the method.
What to do
is up to you.
Will you choose the slim chance of being with the one you love for the rest of your life,
or give up the one you love
for the Three Realms?
Liu Shao.
You must make a choice.
[Chapter About Luo Ge]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 40]
Don't cling to superficial phenomena, don't get stuck in your own heart.
What you see is not necessarily the truth, you have to keep the purity of your heart.
Luo Ge.
This is the solution I leave you with.
What you see is not necessarily the truth, you have to keep the purity of your heart.
Don't cling to superficial phenomena, don't get stuck in your own heart.
I see.
I get it.
On that day,
I agreed to that three-day aggrement,
and I have been looking forward to the magnificence destined
for me ever since.
I have encountered setbacks countless times,
but I have never regretted agreeing to this agreement.
Today,
I am even more glad that I agreed to this agreement.
Congratulations, Supreme God.
Today I will marry the one I love.
No matter what we have to face in the future,
I have no regrets in my life
to be able to marry him.
This is what I promised you,
and it is also my own wish.
You also promised me that you would be with me forever.
Don't you forget.
I won't.
How I wish
this moment
would last forever.
I'm lucky
to marry Liu Shao as my wife.
This is my blessing in this life.
Now that we are husband and wife,
we must stay together forever
and never be separated.
Never be separated.
Even if I turn into a wisp of smoke and dust,
I will follow you.
No.
I don't want smoke and dust.
I only want you, Luo Ge.
Luo Ge.
No, you shouldn't be...
Liu Shao.
I'm sorry.
Luo Ge is so considerate.
I haven't seen him for three days,
and he actually found a wife for me.
Are you waiting for me to come back and enter the bridal chamber together?
That depends on whether you can
stay alive to do that with me.
Do you get so rampant
just because of this formation?
I got an enlightenment from Supreme God.
The solution
is all around me.
Now I have set up a formation to borrow the righteous energy of the Three Realms
to build a boundary beside Xuan Ling Wood.
You can kill that demon
with this formation.
Treat yourself as an ordinary person.
Keep your heart pure.
Don't be distracted by the outside world.
Concentrate on eradicating demons.
The support of Immortal Palace and demon world,
as well as the power of Supreme God Luo Ge
are all in this formation.
You can only use half of your power
here.
It's enough
to deal with you.
Liu Shao.
Time is running out.
Hurry.
Hurry!
Kill me!
Luo Ge.
Luo Ge!
Hurry!
Hurry up.
Keep your sense.
I can definitely find a way to deal with him.
I'll keep it.
Luo Ge!
You're so vile.
There can never be too much deception
in war.
Now I have collected the power of the two Supreme Gods,
God of the Moonlight and Supreme God Luo Ge.
Even if you are supported by formation,
you are unable to defeat me.
You should give up fighting back
and just be my bride obediently.
I am the most powerful person in the Three Realms.
Who else dares to stand against me?
All people in the Three Realms are standing against you.
Luo Ge, wake up!
I know you're still here.
Luo Ge.
All beings in the Three Realms, listen up!
God of the Moonlight has returned
after thousands of years.
From now on you can only call me Supreme God.
I have no other names.
My beloved wife, Immortal Liu Shao,
and I will protect our people together.
From now on,
I will be in charge of life and death in the Three Realms.
Humans, immortals, demons and all living beings must be ruled by me.
Survival is my gift to you,
and death is my reward to you.
This
is my oracle,
and it is also your destiny.
You are not able to kill it by being so soft-hearted.
Even if I will die from the backlash of Moon Sword,
I won't kill you.
No, Liu Shao!
No.
I'm Luo Ge.
How could you do it
just to kill that evil spirit?
How could you kill me?
Luo Ge.
Luo Ge!
Liu Shao.
We all made the same mistakes.
If he is not in Xuan Ling Wood Formation,
the entire Immortal Palace will not be able to defeat him.
Liu Shao.
You have to make a choice.
You're finally awake.
Here.
Drink this.
Have I...
Have I been asleep for long? How is it now?
Do you become stupid due to the beat?
You have been asleep all day and all night.
That demon wanted to establish its majesty,
and had already hurt several generals.
Stop thinking about that guy.
Although your external injuries have healed,
the exhaustion of your internal strength still needs to be recovered.
By the way, Luo Ge had something for you.
This...
is from Luo Ge?
Just a few days before your wedding,
he told me to hand it over to you.
Clear Vine has strong medicinal properties,
and together with Baffling Star Stone,
it can break the previously sealed Sun Spirit
in her body.
Give this to Liu Shao.
She knows what to choose.
Luo Ge wanted me
to break the seal of Sun Spirit?
Will you choose the slim chance of being with the one you love for the rest of your life,
or give up the one you love for the Three Realms?
You have to make a choice.
He can still maintain a trace of sanity?
Why are you doing this?
As long as you submit to me obediently,
I can let you own the Three Realms.
If you really think you can win,
you won't waste your time talking to me here.
Or are you afraid
that you won't be able to control Immortal Palace?
Shut up!
I want you to see the Three Realms
surrender to me.
Farewell.
Guards!
Supreme God.
Summon Immortal Liu Shao
to see me.
When the moon falls,
the Three Realms will probably enter the eternal night.
Brother,
should we go to Immortal Palace to see what happened?
No need. I have already made arrangements.
All of this is because of me.
So I should go.
Just tell me
if there is anything you need me to do.
The future of the demon world
and Melody race still needs you.
Just succeed to Demon King,
if I fail to return.
I don't want to be
the King of this demon world at all.
If you don't want the demon world
to be destroyed by me,
you'd better live for thousands of years
and continue to be Demon King.
Otherwise,
the entire Melody race can be ruined by me.
Why are you still capricious
even for now?
Well...
Probably I will still be capricious this time.
You don't have to be mad at me.
It's not worth it.
Fu.
Fu...
What did you do?
Why did you kill innocent people arbitrarily?
I didn't.
I just asked Shang Yurong
to prepare some fine wine for me.
But he said that there is no wine in Immortal Palace.
Liu Shao.
Don't you think
I should teach them a lesson?
Right.
No matter what,
we have to put Supreme God first.
Bai Feng?
Liu Shao.
Bai Feng has sworn to follow me.
From then on, the grudges between the two of you are over.
Don't mention it in the future.
Okay?
Yes.
Is this why you called me here?
I have something else to do.
I'll leave you two alone.
My sweetheart.
What are you busy with?
Are you busy breaking the seal
and becoming a Supreme God
to deal with me?
What did you do?
I'm just warning you.
Just be my wife obediently.
Don't think about doing useless things.
Also,
tell Shang Yurong and the others
to come to Litian Temple tomorrow morning.
I'm going to make up a grand coronation.
So ungrateful.
I'm the future ruler of the Three Realms.
What is she not satisfied
with being able to marry me?
You treat Liu Shao so kindly.
She should be grateful.
Luo Ge,
I'll show you
how the whole Immortal Palace...
No,
how the entire Three Realms
surrender to me.
Tomorrow
is the coronation for that demon,
and it is also the time for us to help Liu Shao seal him.
This matter concerns the safety of the Three Realms.
I absolutely cannot allow that demon
to use Luo Ge's body
to do whatever he wants in the Three Realms.
If you are of the same mind as me,
please help me
tomorrow.
Why couldn't I become Supreme God
even though the seal has been broken?
What should we do?
Tomorrow
is that demon's coronation.
He knew we were going to do this,
so he must have done something.
Help her absorb the power of Clear Vine first.
We still have a tough battle
to fight.
Hurry up.
-Step aside. -Hurry.
Supreme God.
The feast is still being prepared.
Please enter the hall and wait for a while.
Shang Yurong.
You better not do what you shouldn't do.
With my cultivation,
no matter how hard you try,
it will all be in vain.
I dare not.
Please, Supreme God.
Shang Yurong.
Tell them to hurry up.
I don't like to wait.
Supreme God.
You don't have to wait any longer.
Everyone is ready.
How dare you!
You even really set up a formation to deal with me.
But do you think you really deserve
to be my opponents?
Just give it a try
and you'll know.
Go to hell!
It's time to wake up
from your dream!
Liu Shao.
I thought of a way to save myself.
I have cast a spell into the Moon Bell.
If one day I am completely controlled by evil spirit,
you can wake me up through Wang Bell.
Then you need to seal  evil spirit immediately.
You have learned the way of sealing
in Crown Wheel.
You just need to
find the timing.
Although I failed to get back the power of God of the Sun,
Clear Vine helped me improve a lot.
Now all nightmares are coming to an end.
You are nothing but an evil spirit,
and you are not worthy of being Luo Ge at all.
Luo Ge is really amazing.
Haven't I already suppressed him?
How dare he plot against me?
But
you can't break my forbidden spell.
You can't even
get back Sun Spirit's cultivation.
You are not capable of sealing me.
You're right.
Although I can't get the cultivation back,
Luo Ge and I
have countless fellow disciples and friends behind us.
But what about you?
You have nothing.
Luo Ge.
Well.
Okay.
Then I will let Luo Ge come out for a while.
Listen.
Even if you seal me,
Luo Ge will lose everything
and even his life.
Ge.
Liu Shao.
Luo Ge.
Time is running out.
Just do it as soon as possible.
Everyone,
get ready to set up the formation.
Luo Ge.
Liu Shao.
It's okay.
Luo Ge.
Liu Shao!
How dare you plot against me?
You wanna do it the hard way?
Just wait and see.
I will kill all the people in Immortal Palace
and
make you submit to me.
I just like woman like you.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
I'm not.
Do you think I really surrendered to you before?
You are nothing.
Luo Ge belongs to me alone.
I'm going to avenge Luo Ge now.
Have you forgotten everything?
That Luo Ge
didn't care about you at all,
nor would he smile at you.
I'm the only one
who would smile at someone like you.
Don't flatter yourself.
Who cares about your smile?
You're nothing
but a bunch of nasty black spirits.
I have been waiting for so many days
just to let you die.
It seems that the Three Realms are really coming to an end this time.
No.
I cannot let the Immortal Palace's ten thousand years of foundation
be ruined.
Even if
I cannot defeat him in the end,
it's my honor to fight against the enemy with you
today.
Brother.
Fu.
What are you doing?
Remember I told you
that I would be capricious one more time?
The power of the Demon King!
Fu!
Stop!
The power of the Demon King has merged with your divine spirit.
You will die.
I will die.
But you will survive.
Right?
Fu!
Stop!
Please stop!
If one of us
has to sacrifice his life for the Melody race
or even the Three Realms,
I hope that person will be me.
Melody race
needs a mature and dispassionate Demon King.
Fu!
Brother.
I probably pissed you off again, right?
Fu.
But the mistakes I made
have to be fixed by me,
even if it will cost my life.
Luo Ning.
Brother.
Take care of Luo Ning for me.
Don't go.
Don't!
Black Moonlight.
I will give you back the 30% immortal power
you gave me.
Luo Ning.
Ning!
Fu!
You crazy bastards!
You can't kill me!
Even if I couldn't kill you,
I could suppress you for a moment
with all my water energy.
I'm done with my part.
I'll leave
the rest to you.
Luo Ge!
Luo Ge.
What's wrong?
You think I caused trouble again?
How's your hand?
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'm not worried about you.
Fu.
Come back.
You're the Demon King and my brother!
You are more important
than me.
Come back!
Liu Shao.
Please.
Kill me.
Okay?
Is there
really no other way?
It has long been integrated
with my divine spirit.
I still have the sense
to send you back to the Xuan Ling Wood Formation that day.
This is the last chance.
You must not hesitate.
You're fighting for me.
You must kill me.
This is...
This is the way to the wedding night,
which can help you get back to Xuan Ling Wood Formation.
God of the Sun?
Liu Shao.
You are different from me,
different from us all.
God of the Moonlight has promised you a magnificent life.
You have an extraordinary destiny.
You were never a shadow of me.
You are Liu Shao,
the Liu Shao who was willing to sacrifice herself,
suppressed demons with her talisman pearls,
and surpassed God of the Sun and God of the Moonlight.
I'm back.
You are so rampant
just because of this formation?
God of the Sun?
This is fate.
You will all be defeated by me.
Take a good look at who I am.
Even if my opponent is fate
this time,
I must
win
for Luo Ge
and the Three Realms.
Luo Ge.
No!
Liu Shao.
You did well.
I'll always be with you.
Even...
even if I turned into a wisp of smoke and dust,
I would always be by your side.
Don't be sad.
♫On rainy days, wind blows smoke♫
I'm always here.
♫Into circles♫
I would like to devote my entire life
♫On both sides, I'm chanting♫
to promise you
♫The night is sleepless♫
to be with you forever.
♫The shadows of the moon are incomplete, and people are in love♫
Luo Ge.
♫A cocoon of shadows♫
I'll wait for you to come back.
♫Your promise, my fate♫
We are going to be husband and wife for life.
♫In spring, seasons changed♫
OK.
♫But my heart is still the same♫
I promise you.
♫Back to the sky, the clouds passing by♫
Luo Ge.
♫Is like the things we went through♫
You promised me.
You promised me, Luo Ge.
♫Beside the lake, on the boat♫
You will be back, right?
♫The moment we passed each other♫
♫Can compare with the rest of my life♫
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
♫Looking at your ageless face at the end of the world♫
♫You put the winter snow in your ears and can't hear it♫
♫When the flowers stop falling, you and I will miss each other♫
♫Everything in the world passes before understanding♫
♫After the missing, my face is still young♫
♫The day the flowers fall in the garden, the day we meet♫
♫If you see me for the first time in this life, I'll forever hold it in my heart♫
♫Get lost in your sky♫
♫Whose wilderness♫
♫Clouds billow up and fade away in the four seas♫
♫The mountains and rivers after the farewell♫
♫Silence♫
♫Time sighs silently♫
♫Whose passing years♫
This is Wang Bell.
Don't forget to keep it with you.
If you are in danger in the future,
my Moon Bell will sense it.
Even if I had to go through thousands of calamities and pass through thousands of years,
I would like to devote my entire life
to promise you to be with you forever.
Fate made a joke.
It took me to find you
and forced me to kill you
with my own hands.
Then
it left me alone
in this world.
It made me keep looking for your shadow
in endless memories,
doing things you haven't finished,
and watching
other people's lives.
Are these people who have appeared in my life,
the fickle life
and the flashy love
illusion
or real?
This is the Three Realms you have guarded.
It is now as peaceful and happy
as you ever wished it would be.
♫I want to get close but I can't see clearly♫
Only
♫Who arranged this rain?♫
you are gone.
There is one more heart
in this world
♫I want to avoid but I meet you again♫
that is half missing.
♫I can't help but stay with you♫
I can't feel the joys and sorrows of the world,
and I can't feel the passage of time.
♫The stars call the morning sky♫
I just hope
♫May you feel relieved♫
my dream can come true.
And you
♫I long for a hug♫
♫Can I not just listen?♫
♫I want to find our way through destiny♫
are in that dream.
♫I want to throw away the memory in exchange for you to come back♫
♫Raise the glass to reincarnate the world♫
♫I'll wait for your response with no regrets♫
♫I'll find the promised home for you♫
♫My heart aches and I will say yes again♫
♫When will we separate?♫
♫Please don't tell us our ending in advance♫
[Soon of the Moon]